

CYAN, CHEN 陳智圓

Fullstack Web developer, Entrepreneur

- @ shtomcom@gmail.com
- **J** +886-933024656
- New Taipei City, Taiwan

- in chen-zhi-yuan
- Yukimotochern

STRENGTHS

TypeScript React Redux

tRPC Mono Repo Nx

Prisma Docker Fastify

Express Postgres

MongoDB Python

LaTeX

LANGUAGES

Chinese: Native

English: TOEFL iBT 105

Japanese: N2 level

PROUD OF

useClampText

Link: @yukimoto/use-clamp-text.

ABOUT ME

Self-taught fullstack web developer and entrepreneur. Fast learner and open to new technologies and tools of any languages. Currently maintain the enrollment system for Change Healthcare, the top online payment platform in US. The system is in fullstack TypeScript setup and aims to create a smooth and secure onboarding experience for practice providers.

EXPERIENCE

Senior Web Developer | Innova Solutions, Change Healthcare

2022.05 – Now

- Taipei City, Taiwan
- Responsible for enrollment system along with a support tool for monitoring potential fraud.
- Tech Stack: Nodejs, Typescript Fastify, Postgres, TypeORM, React, Redux.
- Also help to maintain the CI/CD pipe lines which built with Jenkins and the services run on AWS ECS.

Fullstack Web Developer | Touch Whale

2018.09 – 2022.05

- New Taipei City, Taiwan
- Using **MERN** stack web app to facilitate various work flow, like order processing, stock management and marketing decision(scrapper).
- This project use **Javascript** with **Nodejs**, **React**, **Redux** and **MongoDB**. It aims at solving the following problems:
- Order processing: collect data from shopee platform and transform into easy-to-use UI for workers to deal with.
- Marketing decision: use scrapper to get data from shopee platform and generate visual representation.

CEO | Touch Whale | https://shopee.tw/sixstar

2016.10 – 2022.05

- New Taipei City, Taiwan
- Manage the online shop in shopee platform.
- Achieve sales of 200K US dollar in 2021.

EDUCATION

Masters, Computational Physics | National Taiwan University

2017.09 – 2021.06

- Taipei, Taiwan
- No. 1 university in Taiwan
- Using Nelder-Mead algorithm to optimize the entanglement between optical photons and microwave photons through optomechanical interface.

Bachelors, Physics | National Taiwan University

2013.09 – 2017.06

Taipei, Taiwan